Bradley Bain

SUMMARY

Involved in the tech industry since he was a highschooler, Brad has worked for companies ranging from startups like Dialexa to corporate behemoths like Sabre and published his own personal projects online and on the App Store. A student at Pomona College who believes the human side of tech is just as important as the science behind it, Brad is a people person first, developer and designer second.

EDUCATION

Pomona College

BACHELOR OF ARTS, COMPUTER SCIENCE

Claremont, California

Expected Graduation May 2020

3.75 GPA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

(Java, HTML/CSS, Python, Ruby, Node.js, Swift, Git)

Sabre

SABRE LABS SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

May 2017 - Aug 2017; May 2016 - Aug 2016

Proposed, developed, and presented a VR Content Distribution API for Texas Travel Exchange, an industry-wide conference

Presented case study on improving recommendation systems using machine learning

Integrated new web technologies into consumer-facing TripCase app

Dialexa

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

Dec 2016 - Jan 2017; Aug 2015 - May 2016

Full-stack intern working on a multitude of projects on frontend, backend, and Q&A

Created hardware-to-software interface backend for a custom FDA approved spectrometer for Resonant Sensors Labs Group

Pomona

STUDENT WEB ASSISTANT

Aug 2016 - Present

Managed <u>www.pomona.edu</u> and <u>aspc.pomona.edu</u> in conjunction with the Communications Office and Associated Students of Pomona College

EXTRACURRICULARS

CS Teaching Assistant

Mentored students, graded assignments, and proxied labs for "CS 62 - Data Structures" at Pomona College.

Pomona Ventures

Pomona College's entrepreneurship club, connecting students with alumni and venture capitalists in the startup industry

On The Loose

Active participant in Pomona College's outdoor club, helping to plan and organize hiking and camping trips

AWARDS

Eagle Scout

Boy Scouts of America

Goldman Sachs L.A. Symposium Attendee

Selected from a competitive applicant pool to meet and learn from professionals in the finance industry

Harvard Book Award

Awarded by the Harvard Alumni Association each year to a student who demonstrates excellence in studies, character, and achievement

Pomona College Orientation Adventure Leader

Selected to lead a class of incoming freshmen on a 5-day wilderness trip

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Data Structures and Advanced Programming

Pomona College

Discrete Mathematics *Harvey Mudd College*

Linear Algebra in Comp. Science Applications

Brown University

Fundamentals of Computer Science

Pomona College

Principles of Economic Analysis

Claremont McKenna College